Finding Aid for Sam Sturgis Photograph collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Manchester
  - Democratic caucus, township clerk's office circa 1900-1910 1905, M 81 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Southwest Farmer's club meeting., M 82 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Roland and Harold Servis and Colonel in 1910. 1910, M 83 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Alber Cider Mill in 1890 on Bethel Church Road. 1890, M 84 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Matt Blosser, editor and publisher of "Manchester Enterprise" for sixty-five years., M 85 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Matt Blosser in 1870, editor and publisher of "Manchester Enterprise" for sixty-five years. 1870, M 86 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Clarence Knorpp on motorcycle., M 87 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Harvey Rose, daughter and C. Knorpp at 408 E. Main St., M 88 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Passenger F. Huber and driver Clarence Knorpp in old Ford during 1912. 1912, M 89 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Manchester High School graduating class in 1909. 1909, M 90 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Teacher Kitty Weir's first and second grade in 1898. 1898, M 91 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (* Boy in fourth seat on right in Clayton Parr, later town supervisor for over twenty years. Published.)
  - Freight office., M 92 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - GA Fausel Jewelry Store in 1887 with family in front and residence above, corner Riverside and Exchange Place. 1887, M 93 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Saturday Club (all women), charter members., M 94 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Mayor's Day on 20 May 1957. 1957, M 95 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Left to right: Bennet Root, RB Hauessler, Fred Lehman, Arthur Jenter, Ed Dresselhouse, Tosselo Knorpp, George Merriman. Published.)
  - Old Ward School on Main St. in 1893. 1893, M 96 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - G. Koebbe Threshing Machine during 1900S. Women cooked for the crew., M 97 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. bridge before dam and mill with Mr. Brown's gristmill at right., M 98 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - GT Hauessler's Victorian living room in Fountain House between 1890 and 1910. circa 1900, M 99 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Raisin River looking north to dam and mill., M 100 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Looking west from water tower hill during 1890s, with Towne's Apple Drying House in left foreground, ice house in center. circa 1895, M 101 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Unter Kircher Block during 1890s. GT Hauessler, WH Puttle. circa 1895, M 102 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Hauessler & Kingsley Drug Store during 1880s. circa 1885, M 103 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Advertisement for Care Threshing Machine, "Steam Engine and Steel separator, $880.00.11, M 104 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Loading hay., M 105 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Interior Wuerthner Clothing Store on 26 December 1908. 1908, M 106 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Scenic view in 1872. 1872, M 107 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - The 20th-Century Club, a women's club., M 108 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - William and Mary Carr portrait c. Civil War., M 109 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Scenic view of east Manchester., M 110 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Rowe's Corners School, erected 1880., M ill --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Township Library., M 112 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Dr. James Lynch built as home in 1867, purchased by township in 1934 for library. Published.)
  - Shakespeare Club portrait, a women's club., M 113 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Bill Baxter in 1901. Came to Manchester in 1837 and owned dry goods store on Exchange Place since that year. 1901, M 114 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - shipping sheep in 1915. 1915, M 115 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Portrait of Grant Sutton family in horse and carriage in front of home., M 116 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Marie Kirchhofer, high school principal in 1885. 1886, M 117 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Two blacksmiths in Schneider's Blacksmith Shop c. 1900. circa 1900, M 118 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Farmers Higgins and Weinlander at celery harvest west of Manchester., M 119 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Sale bill for Gilbert farm during 1890s. circa 1895, M 120 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - J. Schneider, Manchester's last blacksmith, May 1946. 1946, M 121 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - War veterans reunion., M 122 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - J. Weiss Shoe Shop., M 123 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Independence Day program. Date in previous finding aid says 1839. Probably closer to latter half of 19th century., M 124 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - "The German Church," common name for Trinity Evangelical Lutheran Church, built 1872., S 1 --; Copy neg.
  - Baptist Church, replaced another church in 1904. Cement blocks by Elwood Rogers. Later site of the public library., S 2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Saline baseball team in 1908 or 1909. 1909, S 3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
- Saline
  - Chicago St. residence in 1911. 1911, S 4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Bridge, dam and Saline River in 1909(?). 1909, S 5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Orange Risdon home, built in 1829 on hill in center. Home later moved to Henry St. and modernized in 1948. Published.)
  - East Main St. in 1914. "Old Maude" entering village on E. Michigan Ave. 1914, S 6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - South side Main (St. Before 1900, photo includes Burkhardt's, new store in center and Sy Cotton's Grocery, third building from corner.) circa 1895, S 7 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - South side Main St. in 1911. 1911, S 8 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Specimens of wool producers, photo from post card mailed 1913. 1913, S 9 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Methodist Church, third building built 1899., S 10 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Slaughterhouse perched on edge of Saline River and overlooking mill pond on Chicago Turnpike., S 11 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking east from interurban transforming station on E. Michigan Ave., built 1899., S 12 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - De Puy residence in 1929 on S. Macon Road. 1929, S 13 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Curtis-Davenport residence., S 14 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Main St. looking east., S 15 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Corner Ann Arbor and McKap Sts. looking east along 200 block of Michigan Ave in 1908. 1908, S 16 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Bandwagon built 1874 by Schairer Bros for Centennial. Photo from tintype. 1874, S 17 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Residence., S 18 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Looking east on Michigan Ave. from Saline Y-DSR interurban in 1908. Cop~ neg. Published. 1908, S 19 -- (Box 5)
  - Risdon House., S 20 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - New residence of Mrs. Jane Harper in 1893. 1893, S 21 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - New residence of Mrs. HR Watson in 1893. 1893, S 22 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Saline Union School, built 1868 at N. Ann and McKay Sts. Photo taken 1893. 1893, S 23 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Scene on Chicago Turnpike., S 24 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Teachers in the Saline School in 1870. 1870, S 25 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (See Old Saline Village for full list of names. Published.)
  - Saline Mills in 1972. 1972, S 26 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Stone house., S 27 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Monroe St. c. 1911. 1911, S 28 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Saline founder, Orange Risdon honored. Left to right: Blanche Mead, Mayor Henry Leutheuser, Mrs. Anne Boyer, Dr F. Clever Bald, Howell Taylor on 29 June 1954. 1954, S 29 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Chicago St. looking east., S 30 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - D.J. & C. Snow Plow (train car), Detroit, Jackson and Chicago Railway Saline division during February 1912. 1912, S 31 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Presbyterian parsonage c. 1870, still standing at 307 N. Ann Arbor St. circa 1870, S 32 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Corner Chicago Road and Adrian St. in 1893. 1893, S 33 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Portrait of Orange Risodon, founder of Saline., S 34 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Mrs. Orange Risdon, wife of Saline founder., S 35 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Planting potatoes at Saline Valley Farms., S 36 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Feeding chickens at Saline Valley Farms., S 37 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Raising broilers at Saline Valley Farms., S 38 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - View from Center Mill Pond after or 1929. circa 1930, S 39 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Harold Gray (at right) lifting ch onto Saline Valley Farms hay wago, S 40 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Barn at Saline Valley Farms. Cop neg., S 41 -- (Box 5)
  - Dairy truck and driver from Salin Valley Farms., S 42 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Old farm house. Russell Mills on Chicago Turnpike., S 43 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Railroad track on Saline town str, S 44 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Jacob Sturm's Harness Shop on Chi Turnpike. Photo from tintype. C neg. Published., S 45 -- (Box 5)
  - Fosdich School on Bemis Road. Cc neg. Published., S 46 -- (Box 5)
  - [Undescribed], S 47 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Walker residence on Bemis Road. neg. Published., S 48 -- (Box 5)
  - Residence., S 49 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Muir and Gross Hardware in June I 1911, S 50 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Interior Muir and Gross Hardware., S 51 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Older woman standing next to pair, S 52 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Saline Garage, later site of par lot adjacent to St. Paul's Church, S 53 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Herd of cows., S 54 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Independence Day parade in 1894. 1894, S 55 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Hoyt School, built prior to 1857 on Macon Road. In 1943, Henry Ford moved school to 600 W. Michigan Ave. as private residence., S 56 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - River and dam., S 57 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
- Ypsilanti
  - Business section on Huron St., Y 1 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Gymnasium at Michigan State Normal School, 1908 postmark. 1908, Y 2 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Gilbert Park., Y 3 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published Source: Wystan Stevens. Published.)
  - President's residence at Michigan State Normal School in 1910. 1910, Y 4 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Conservatory at Michigan State Normal School in 1908. 1908, Y 5 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - The Normal Book Store at Cross St. and College Place, near Michigan State Normal School with owner George Zweigel in front., Y 6 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Starkweather Hall at Michigan State Normal School on Forest St., Y 7 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Central fire station, Ypsilanti Fire Department., Y 8 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cross St. in 1915. 1915, Y 9 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Water tower in 1907. 1907, Y 10 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Science building at Michigan State Normal School in 1910. 1910, Y 11 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Training School at Michigan State Normal School., Y 12 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cleary Business College., Y 13 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Recreation Park in 1912 with early airplane. 1912, Y 14 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Training School and Stand Tower in 1911. 1911, Y 15 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Prospect Park in 1911. 1911, Y 16 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congress St. east on 13 January 190 now Michigan Ave. looking east from Washington St. with early automobile 1908, Y 17 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Source: Wys Stevens.)
  - Southwest corner Washington and Congress Sts., Y 18 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Huron River Bridge on Congress St., now Michigan Ave., Y 19 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Octagon House on River St., built c 1850, moved 1860s., Y 20 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Michigan Central Railroad depot. C neg., Y 21 --; . (Box 5)
  - Huron Street., Y 22 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published Source: MHC.)
  - Congress St., now Michigan Ave., with horse and carriage., Y 23 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congress Hotel and GL Thornton Real Estate (or general store) c. 1900. circa 1900, Y 24 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Source: MHC)
  - Seth Reed, 100 years old, 1823-1923 in front of log cabin repro. for Y Centennial celebration. 1923, Y 25 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Jenness residence on Forest Ave. i 1892. 1892, Y 26 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Sour e Art Work 1892.)
  - Underwear Mills. 1892, Y 27 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Source: Art Work 1892.)
  - Congress St., now Michigan Ave. in 1892. 1892, Y 28 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Looking south from Congress St. Br to the Deubel Bros. Mill. Copy neg Published. 1892, Y 29 --; . (Box 5)
    (Source: Art Work 1892.)
  - Michigan Central Railroad depot c. 1890. 1892, Y 30 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Bank block or YMCA or YWCA(?) c. I 1892, Y 31 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Source: A Work 1892.)
  - Michigan Central Railroad depot pa c. 1890. 1892, Y 32 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: Art 1892.)
  - Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Interurban car, called "Ypsi-Ann.11, Y 33 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Source:MHC .)
  - Detroit, Ann Arbor, Jackson and Ypsilanti RR garage, power house f line between Detroit and Jackson i 1907. 1907, Y 34 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Source MHC.)
  - First steam fire engine, purchased 1870., Y 35 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congress St. or Huron St. looking in 1893. 1893, Y 36 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First brick school, erected in 1829. still standing behind newer Woodruff School., Y 37 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Bridge and Ypsi Grain & Elevator Co., formerly the Deubel Mill. Lg. building on right is Follett House, hotel on MCRR between Detroit and Chicago., Y 38 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Detroit, Ann Arbor, Ypsilanti and Jackson Railroad waiting room and freight room., Y 39 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congress St., later Michigan Ave., looking east with City Cash Store., Y 40 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Panoramic view of Ypsi pre-Civil War(?)., Y41 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Train in winter., Y 42 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congress St. looking east., Y 43 --; Copy neg (Box 5)
  - Southwest corner Washington and Congress Sts., Y 44 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congress St. looking east., Y 45 --; Copy neg (Box 5)
  - View on Huron River., Y 46 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published Source: MHC .)
  - Gas station at corner of Park St., Y 47 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cleary Business College., Y 48 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - WH McDermott Horse Shoeing and Carriage Works, next door to Ypsilanti Auto Parts., Y 49 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti interurban, called "Ypsi-Ann"., Y 50 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - F. Fletcher - old map., Y 51 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Owen Mineral Wells, located on later site of Roosevelt Hotel., Y 52 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - saloon interior of George W, Cady third from right, at 56 East Cross St., Y 53 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Sweet's Dry Goods Store., Y 54 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Owen Mineral Wells., Y 55 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Charles McLaughey building bridge at Frain or French Landing c. 1890. circa 1890, Y 56 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - The Ypsilantian - Left to right: Tracey L. Towner, ?, Fred W. Green., Y 57 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - City reservoir., Y 58 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published. Photographer: Carrie A. Hardy. Source: MHC.)
  - Car wrecked at Hewitt Rd. west of Ypsi after hitting an eastbound truck in 1923. 1923, Y 59 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Interurban train and crew at station., Y 60 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Looking west on Congress St., now Michigan Ave., from Prospect St. in 1908. 1908, Y 61 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - East side of Ypsilanti power house on 23 January 1907. 1907, Y 62 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Early electric car (interurban) operating between Ann Arbor and Ypsilanti., Y 63 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Car House on 12 January 1915. 1915, Y 64 --; Copy neg.
  - Ypsilanti Power House from Congress St. bridge on 23 January 1907. 1907, Y 65 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First interurban trip to Ann Arbor or 26 November 1896. Called "Ypsi-Ann" line. 1896, Y 66 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Detroit,Jackson and Chicago Railroad power house on 23 January 1907. 1907, Y 67 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Detroit, Jackson and Chicago Railroad power house from Michigan Ave * bridge., Y 68 --; Copy neg (Box 5)
  - Detroit, Jackson and Chicago Railroad office building on NW corner River Street and E. Michigan Ave. on 23 Jan 1907. 1907, Y 69 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Interurban, Detroit, Jackson and Chicago Railroad crews., Y 70 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Source: MH)
  - Ypsilanti Dairy Creamery Company at end Race St. near south side Spring St., Y 71 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Early fire company members' names., Y 72 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Masonic Temple stone-laying in 1909. 1909, Y 73 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Fire Department station at N. Washington and W. Cross Sts. in 1909. 1909, Y 74 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First school stack at Normal College, Y 75 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Presbyterian Church, 1859 and view o Ypsilanti. 1859, Y 76 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Clara J. Drury and Fred K. Peas Minuet Club in 1894. 1894, Y 77 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Maccabee float on July 4, 1899 Barbara Disbrow on float. Cop Published. 1899, Y 78 -- (Box 5)
  - Joseph H. Thompson, Inc. Dodge at 206 Michigan Ave. in 1930. Includes Elmer King, Ed Squire Nelson Belaugh, Harry Smith an Thompson. 1930, Y 79 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
    (Published)
  - Ypsilanti Gas Works on 12 April 1916, Y 80 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Recreation during Spanish-Amer encampment., Y 81 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Whist Club in 1902. Agnes Mithews, Mrs. JH Tepper! Henry. Others: Mrs. LM James Bornstula, Mrs. Charles Childs, HR Scovill. 1902, Y 82 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Scenic view, 1865. 1865, Y 83 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Winning float in Liberty Day celebration parade on 26 April 1918, Y 84 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - HMS Pinafore cast., Y 85 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Alley Fiesta Circus, benefit of Cross, on July 3-6, 1918. Beh Michigan Ave. Stores on north near Washington St. 1918, Y 86 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - [Undescribed], Y 87 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti 1923 Centennial cele Driver Joseph E. Warner and passenger, LA Seamans in old s coach. 1923, Y 88 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Interurban., Y 89 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Going to war on 26 April 1898. neg. 1898, Y 90 -- (Box 5)
  - WHL Roberts Tavern with horse and carriage out front., Y 91 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Accident on New York Central Railroad at Ypsilanti., Y 92 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Company G, First Regiment. MTS return from Island Lake Camp, summer 1895 or 1898. Looking west on Cross St. from NE corner Washington St. 1898, Y 93 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First brick school erected 1829, rear of Woodruff School., Y 94 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cornwell Paper Mill c. 1875 at Lowell St. circa 1875, Y 95 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Peninsular Ice Co. wagon on 9 Sept. 1866. 1866, Y 96 --; Copy neg.
  - Thompson Farm Machinery in 1891. (Building used as barracks during Civil War.) 1891, Y 97 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congress St. looking west in 1907 including new interurban train. 1907, Y 98 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - C. King and Company grocery store at corner Congress and Huron Sts. Congress St., now Michigan Ave., Y 99 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Automobile with group of men in 1915. 1915, Y 100 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - moved to Ann Arbor series., Y 101-Y-101 -- (Box 5)
  - women picnicking at Whitmore Lake during August 1897. With bicycle. Ella Spencer, Nan Babbit, Lee Milhaus and Alice Babbit. 1897, Y 102 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Spanish-American War soldiers c. 1900. circa 1900, Y 103 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Early automobile, Raleigh Hoobler. Bessie Goodspeed., Y 104 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Y-105 moved to Ann Arbor series., Y 105 -- (Box 5)
  - Second high school., Y 106 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Michigan Central Railroad and Lake Shore Station., Y 107 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Early portrait of children., Y 108 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Company G, 31st Infantry, battalion from Span-An War. circa 1900, Y 109 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Michigan Central Railroad engine at Ypsilanti, late 1880s. circa 1890, Y 110 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Huron St. in 1893. 1893, Y ill --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Congress St. scene, now Michigan Av during fall-winter 1900. 1900, Y 112 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Company G, 31st Infantry, Spanish-American War. circa 1900, Y 113 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Store interior., Y 114 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - store interior. Left to right: Jo Lamb, Elihu Gooding., Y 115 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cadaret's Grocery in 1914 at 112 Michigan Ave. Left to right: ?, Mrs. John Cadaret, Miss Marjorie Hancock John William Cadaret. 1914, Y 116 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - The "little white schoolhouse" before remodeling as Dr. FE Westfall's residence., Y 117 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Woodruff School in 1916. 1916, Y 118 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti High School baseball team champions in 1895. 1895, Y 119 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti High School football team 1906. 1906, Y 120 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti High School baseball team in 1908. 1908, Y 121 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - First post office in Ypsilanti., Y 122 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Milling Co., Y 123 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Huron Mills on east side Huron Rd. south of Michigan Ave. bridge with William H. Deubel in foreground., Y 124 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - RR Gardens. Left to right: Damon (agent), Lillian Damon, Jessie Swaine, FJ Swaine., Y 125 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ridgewood Hospital (Leland San?)., Y 126 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ladies Library in 1929, built 1859. 1929, Y 127 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Race car accident at Michigan Ave. bridge., Y 128 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Hawkins House c. 1860, NW corner Congress (Michigan Ave.) and Washington Sts., Y 129 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Interior, YWCA room., Y 130 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Lewis-Geer Manufacturing Company on 12 April 1916. Roller bearings, coaster wagons ideal auto trays. 1916, Y 131 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Hay Press Co. and Flour Mill Machinery on 12 April 1916. 1916, Y 132 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Michigan Ladder Co. in 12 April 1916. 1916, Y 133 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Peninsular Paper Company on 12 April 1916. 1916, Y 134 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Water Works on 12 April 1916. 1916, Y 135 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Machine Works on 12 Apr 1916. 1916, Y 136 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Soldiers on Michigan Ave., return from Span-Am War on 22 Feb. 1900. 1900, Y 137 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Grand Army of the Republic (GAR) encampment in 1911. 1911, Y 138 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - cutting ice and loading on Michigan Central Railroad c. 1915. circa 1915, Y 139 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Cast of "Doctor of Alacantara,11 c opera given by Royal Arch Masons, Ypsilanti Opera House on 14 April 1909. 1909, Y 140 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Opera House stage after cyclone on 12 April 1893. copy n Published. 1893, Y 141 -- (Box 5)
  - "Grandma" Eaton's residence on left after cyclone - moved 7 ft. off foundation. High Street chapel on left on 12 April 1893. 1893, Y 142 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - interior Ypsi Opera House and rea Hawkins House after cyclone, 12 1893. 1893, Y 143 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Curtis Carriage Factory at SW cor S. Adams and Congress Sts. after cyclone, 12 April 1893. 1893, Y 144 --; Copy neg (Box 5)
  - Cyclone, Huron St., 12 April 1893, Y 145 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Huron St. after cyclone, photo ta am on 13 April 1893. 1893, Y 146 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - North Huron St. at Pearl St. after cyclone on 12 April 1893. 1893, Y 147 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Huron St. after cyclone on 12 April 1893. 1893, Y 148 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Ypsilanti Opera House after cyclone 12 April 1893, Y 149 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Water tower in 1893, Y 150 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Unfinished Water Tower, unknown man in the foreground 1893, Y 151 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
  - Manchester Hardware store, Y 152 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
Subject Index: A-D
1901 Council
DE 15
A & P
AA 557, AA 684, AA 685, CM 9
Abel
AA 221.3
Accidents
AA 1A, AA 1B, AA 7, AA 8, AA 9, AA 33, AA 95, AA 96, AA 98, AA 99, AA 100, AA 101, AA 138